webdesign.com 2019-06-16

# 

## Privacy Policy

(updated May 24, 2018)

Welcome to this Digimedia.com, L.P. ("Digimedia") website. This policy describes the information collected on this website and how it may be used and/or shared. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not utilize this website. 

**_Regarding IP Addresses and Other Data._ ** Digimedia and/or third parties may collect your IP address, browser user agent, referral website, and a cookie id. 

**_Regarding Cookies._ ** Digimedia and/or third parties may be placing or reading "cookies" on your internet browser. Cookies are bits of text transferred to your computer hard drive through your browser. They allow Digimedia and/or third party systems to recognize your browser, remember your information and link your activities to you. Should you block or disable these cookies, this website may not work and/or appear as intended. Nevertheless, if you want to take these steps, you can do so by following instructions related to your browser. Cookies may collect types of information such as the following: 

  * Website traffic (for example: the domain name and host from which you access the internet and the internet address of the website from which you came to ours),
  * Statistical data and analytics (for example: the date and time you access our website, the keywords and/or links clicked, and/or the pages you visit),
  * Browsing behavior (for example: the pages you visit, the services or products you sought, and/or products/services you purchased)
  * Information about the operating system, device, platform and web browser type/version you utilize,
  * Demographic information & other non-personal information about you,
  * Advertisement information, and/or
  * Information to fight fraud or misuse.

**_Regarding Personal Information._ ** Some Digimedia websites may collect personal information when you choose to voluntarily provide it via an email, a contact form, a registration form or when purchasing a service or product. This type of information may include your name, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers. 

**_Regarding Sensitive Information._ ** Some Digimedia websites may, as part of your purchase of a product or service, collect sensitive information, such as your credit card number or other financial information. In such case, sensitive information will be encrypted and protected with SSL, the current industry standard encryption protocol. You will know you are on such an SSL page when you see a picture of a closed lock at the bottom or top of some Web browsers. Another way to tell if you are on a secure page is to look at the address or URL of the page. (Look in the address box or right-click on the page and select "Properties".) These secure SSL encrypted pages have URLs that start with https:// instead of http://. 

**_Regarding Digimedia's Use of Information Collected._ ** Information Digimedia collects pursuant to this Privacy Policy may be used to deliver, administer, update and improve the website, services and/or products provided to you, including enhancement and optimization of the website, assessment and diagnosis of potential issues and/or risks such as errors, security risks, fraudulent activity and/or abusive activity, gather broad demographic information, and may be used to aggregate statistics and analytics from the website. Digimedia may share information with third parties as described in the "Regarding Information Collected by Third Parties" section below. Digimedia may use and/or retain your Personal Information (name, email address, address, and/or phone number) to identify you, to reply and/or contact you in reference to an inquiry, assistance request, to manage and/or promote our relationship with you, and/or for other legal and/or legitimate business purposes. 

**_Regarding the Storage, Security and Retention of Information Collected._ ** Digimedia transfers, stores and protects information collected utilizing SSL (see also the "Regarding Sensitive Information" section above) or other generally accepted industry standards. Digimedia retains such information for as long as necessary to provide its service(s) to you or for other legitimate and/or legal purposes. 

**_Regarding Information Collected by Third Parties._ ** This website may consist of third-party advertising, links to other websites, and/or content from third parties. Digimedia may share non-personal (for example: demographic) information to facilitate the delivery of relevant content and/or advertisements. Third party websites, businesses, advertisers, or advertising entities working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to deliver the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons, and other technologies that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites or businesses are not covered by this Privacy Policy but are covered by their respective privacy policies. For Google's policy, please visit the following: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites.](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) Some, but not all, third party advertising companies provide a mechanism to opt-out of their technology. For more information and identification of advertisers that provide an opt-out mechanism, please visit the following: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**_Regarding European Economic Area Visitors._ ** If you are a visitor/customer from the European Economic Area, and you wish to view, update, delete, or transfer your personal information, or if you wish to withdraw consent and/or otherwise exercise your rights pursuant to the GDPR, please email privacy@digimedia.com. 

**_Regarding Ownership and Transfer of Information._ ** Subject to applicable law, all information collected on this website is considered to be an asset of Digimedia and as such may be shared and/or transferred as described in this policy and/or as part of a merger or acquisition (or contemplated merger or acquisition) of Digimedia and/or this website. 

**_Regarding changes to this policy._ ** Digimedia may alter this policy from time to time, so you are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy periodically. 

**_Legal Disclaimer._ ** Digimedia may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or to comply with a legal process served on Digimedia and/or this website. 

If you have further questions, send an email to privacy@digimedia.com.
